<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Draw Veling</title>
    <link>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Draw Veling</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 17:19:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Love and the Care Given Makes You Eternal Not Your Bank Statement</title>
      <link>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/posts/2019/04/28/the-love-and-the-care-given-makes-you-eternal-not-your-bank-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 16:49:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/posts/2019/04/28/the-love-and-the-care-given-makes-you-eternal-not-your-bank-statement/</guid>
      <description>With today’s illustration (pencil + ink pens) I wanted to represent the madness of accumulating wealth although you cannot take it with you once you are dead (the coffin). In contrast with that the shadow and some examples of taking care of someone else.
The ancient Egyptians believed that the afterlife would be perfect. When they entered the afterlife, they wanted to take treasures from their life with them, and small amulets to keep them safe.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Education Is the Only Antidote to Poverty</title>
      <link>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/posts/2019/04/21/education-is-the-only-antidote-to-poverty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 16:36:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/posts/2019/04/21/education-is-the-only-antidote-to-poverty/</guid>
      <description>In the above illustration – as usual, I have first outlined the drawing with pencils and then finished it with ink pens – I wanted to represent how culture helps you climb the ladder of life.
“Still despite their circumstances, Morrie was taught to love and care. And to learn. Eva would accept nothing less than excellence in school, because she saw education as the only antidote to their poverty”. From the book “Tuesday with Morrie” – Mitch Albom</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Run Run Outrun</title>
      <link>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/posts/2019/04/14/run-run-outrun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 16:54:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/posts/2019/04/14/run-run-outrun/</guid>
      <description>Run, run … outrun “Every morning in Africa, a gazelle wakes up, it knows it must outrun the fastest lion or it will be killed. Every morning in Africa, a lion wakes up. It knows it must run faster than the slowest gazelle, or it will starve. It doesn’t matter whether you’re the lion or a gazelle-when the sun comes up, you’d better be running.” Christopher McDougall, Born to run.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Home Is Where Your Heart Is</title>
      <link>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/posts/2019/04/07/home-is-where-your-heart-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 16:56:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/posts/2019/04/07/home-is-where-your-heart-is/</guid>
      <description>This drawing – pencil and then outlined with ink pens – is inspired by the different houses that I have lived in during my 32 years of life on this planet.
Via Curinello: I lived in my parent’s house (top left corner) for the first 19 years of my life, since 1986. From time to time, between adventures, I return there and it’s always a strange mix of different feelings. Even though my deepest fears often resurface when I am there, there is also this unbelievable sense of safety or protection, particularly at night.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Where to Begin</title>
      <link>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/posts/2019/03/31/where-to-begin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 17:02:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensix.github.io/draw-veling/posts/2019/03/31/where-to-begin/</guid>
      <description>ENGLISH: I have decided to begin my blog with my personal beginning.
This pencil drawing of a simple landscape was inspired by a picture taken during Easter 2018. It is a picture of a small house up in the mountains, above the little village where I was born, in 1986.
I left home in 2005 and moved to Perugia to pursue the dream of a better life by obtaining a bachelor’s and a master’s degree.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>